crackspider.net 2014-06-25

# Welcome to Crackspider.net! Search cracks, crackz, serial numbers, serials, keygens and patches for appz, games, torrent for pc,mac,pda software unlock codes!

## Privacy Statement for CRACKSPIDER!

We has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website 

### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used in creating a logging system which counts unique hits. 

### Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. We do not use cookies in other parts of our Web site or as information for ourselves. 

### Partnership

You are welcome to place our [search box and banners](http://crackspider.net/link2us.shtml) to your sites. Also you can integrate our search results via [XML gateway](http://crackspider.net/link2us.shtml)

### Personal Information

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. We not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us via [web form](http://crackspider.net/contact.shtml)
